Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
  - Geneva Agricultural Experiment Station. Barton, Donald W.; Schaefer, Arnold E.; Einset, John; Buck, Paul A.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; New York State College of Agriculture, Interdepartmental Committee on Nutrition and National Defense; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, Experiment Station Club., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Wine Project, Geneva. Taylor, Greyton H.; Hand, David B.; Fournier, Charles; Reveal, Ernest I.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Widmer's Wine Cellars, Inc.; Taylor Wine Company; Wine industry., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Professor Edward Smith, Geneva, Headship, North Carolina. Smith, Edward H.; Brooks, James; North Carolina State Univ., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Extension. Johnson, Alvin A.; Durfee, Arthur E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Extension. Durfee, Arthur E.; Brady, Nyle C.; Johnson, Alvin A.; Fortmann, Henry R.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service-Tennessee Valley Authority; Sugar beet industry., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Sabbatic Leaves for County Extension Personnel. Durfee, Arthur E., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Extension Service, In-Service Training Program. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Curriculum for Subject Matter Training School for Assistant County Agricultural Agents. Swan, John C., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - County Agents Salaries, Increased Support Request. Johnson, Alvin A.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Extension, County Agricultural Agents. Gortzig, Carl F.; Morris, Fred B.; Matott, Howard W.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "The Role of Cooperative Extension Service in New York State." New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Extension Service Statewide Conference of Professional Personnel. Perkins, James A.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Comparative Extension Education Program. Leagans, J. Paul; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education, Div. of Extension Education., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Extension Service, Assistant Director of Marketing. Johnson, Alvin A.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Project M. Hislop, Milton E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service, Project M., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Extension Teaching and Information. Ward, William B.; Shields, Donald J.; Watkins, Thomas C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Extension Teaching and Information., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - State Agricultural Leaders. Swan, John C.; Preston, James C., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - New Position, Associate Director of Programs. Harrington, Clifford R.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - J. Paul Leagans, Extension Personnel. Leagans, J. Paul; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Extension Service, Salaries. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Extension Dairy Program for New York State., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 4-H Club. Pease, Wilbur F.; Four-H Club., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 4-H Club Drop-out Program. Pease, Wilbur F.; Four-H Club., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - County 4-H Agents. Durfee, Arthur E., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - State 4-H Leaders, Sweet, Stout, etc. Durfee, Arthur E.; Pease, Wilbur F., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Extension Committee on 4-H Work., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - University Faculty. Mackesey, Thomas W.; Watkins, Thomas C.; Cornell University, University Faculty., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Major Leaves of Members of the Faculty., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Faculty of the College of Agriculture. Watkins, Thomas C., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Agriculture Faculty by Age, Rank, and Institution of Graduation., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Farm Management Tour to Hudson Valley., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture. Seeley, John G.; Boodley, James W.; Fox, Raymond T.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Foreign Correspondence. National Association for Foreign Student Affairs., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Special Survey of Foreign Students at Cornell in Agriculture and Veterinary College., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Orientation of Foreign Students. Morris, Fred B., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Foreign Visitors Contact Office. Turk, Kenneth L.; Morris, Fred B.; International Agricultural Development; Cornell University, Office of Foreign Visitors., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Freshman Orientation., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Apple Industry Outlook, College Committee Study. New York State College of Agriculture, Fruit Committee; Apple industry., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Gallo, Peter. Gallo, Francis P., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Geiselmann, Harrison. French, Orval C.; Stutz, Frederick H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Hedlund Report, Market Structure., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Gifts to College of Agriculture, Gift and Grant Report., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Graduate School. Hartman, John D.; Cornell University, Graduate School., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Graduates, September and February., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Hall, Donald J., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Hardison, Marcia L. Hertel, John P., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Gifts. Fahnestock, William; Trimberger, George W., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; New York State College of Home Economics., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Ho-Nun-De-Kah. Watkins, Thomas C.; Feddema, Leonard W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Ho-Nun-De-Kah., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - International Agricultural Development. Turk, Kenneth L.; Mellor, John W.; New York State College of Agriculture, International Agricultural Development., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - International Agricultural Development. Turk, Kenneth L.; Mellor, John W.; Ford Foundation; American Freedom From Hunger Campaign; New York State College of Agriculture, International Agricultural Development., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - IAD Proposal to Permit Professors on Sabbatical Leave to Serve Cornell's Overseas Program. New York State College of Agriculture, International Agricultural Development., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Interfraternity Council., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Library., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Livestock Judging Team, Miller Review. Miller, John I., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Livestock Advisory Council., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Los Banos. Turk, Kenneth L.; Umali, D.L.; Velasco, Jose R.; Bradfield, Richard; Rockefeller Foundation; World Bank; Univ. of the Philippines; New York State College, of Agriculture, Los Banos Project., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Los Banos, Applicants for Possible Employment., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Contract, Cornell, Los Banos, Ford Foundation Project. Ford Foundation; Univ. of the Philippines., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Dean Umali's Address to Faculty. Umali, D.L.; Ford Foundation; Rockefeller Foundation., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Philippine Project. Philippines., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Mailings., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Mann Library Fire. Powell, Whiton; Seeley, John G., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Program for Marketing and Business Management Extension, Research and Teaching, Hedlund and Metz Report. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Metz, Joseph F., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Professor Harry MacDonald. MacDonald, Henry A.; Shirley, Hardy L.; New York State College of Forestry., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - W.I. Myers. Myers, William I.; Fox, Edith M., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Graduate School of Nutrition. Barnes, Richard H.; Cornell University, Graduate School of Nutrition; Farm labor., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Overseas Programs, College of Agriculture. Corson, Dale R., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Personnel Office. Willers, Diedrich K.; Cornell University, Personnel Office., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Cornell University Placement Service., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Plant Breeding. Murphy, Royse P.; Ma, Paul C.; Miller, Roberts W.; Srb, Adrian M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Breeding., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Plant Pathology. Parker, Kenneth G.; Dimock, A.W.; Kent, George C.; Boothroyd, Carl W.; Korf, Richard P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Pathology; Fruit industry; Gibberellin., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Cornell Plantations. O'Connor, Audrey H.; Rockwell, George H.; Wright, T.P.; Seeley, John G.; Dunlop, David R.; Cornell Plantations; Cornell Plantations Committee., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Pomology. Hoffman, Melvin B.; Einset, John; Powell, Lloyd E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Pomology., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Poultry Husbandry. Bruckner, Jacob H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Poultry Husbandry; New York State Poultry Council., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Stafford and Genesee County Property. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Poultry Husbandry., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Poultry Industry, Tour. Ostrander, Charles E., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Poultry Servicemen's Clinic., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Program Review Proposal., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Publications, Cooper Report. Cooper, J. Francis; Ward, William B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Publications Committee; "Cornell Recommends.", 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Radiation Safety Office., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Cornell University, Research Club., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Research Report., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Research Associates, Grades., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Resident Instruction. Watkins, Thomas C.; Hertel, John P.; Harden, Leigh H.; Kenyon, Roger B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Resident Instruction. Watkins, Thomas C.; Hertel, John P.;' Gallo, Francis P.; Manso, Peter; Donlon, Mary H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - NIH Grant. Scott, Milton J.; National Institute of Health., 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Resident Instruction Research Reports. New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Review Panel, College of Agriculture. Colman, Gould P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Review Panel., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Rice Debate., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Rural Education. Stutz, Frederick H.; McConkie, George; Hills, R.J.; Mink, Oscar; Downing, Lester N.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Rural Sociology. Larson, Olaf F.; Wakely, Ray E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Sociology., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rural Sociology, Report, Cornell Student Life. Taietz, Philip., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Rural Sociology, Staff Recruitment. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Sociology., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Safety Division., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University Salary Adjustment Across the Board, 1 FEB 1964. Perkins, James A., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Salaries and Policies., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Social Sciences Research Center., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Staff List, College of Agriculture. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Student Government., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Income Tax Recovery by Graduate Assistants., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Tuition and Fees, College of Agriculture., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Tuition and Student Incentive Plans., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Uihlein Farm. Uihlein, Henry., 1961-64 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Vegetable Crops. Munger, Henry M.; Johannessen, George A.; Oyer, Edwin B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Vegetable Crops; United Arab Republic; Potato industry., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural History, Warren Biography. Warren, George F.; Colman, Gould P.; LaMont, Thomas E.; Biggerstaff, Knight; Gates, Paul W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Oral History Project., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - A Miscellaneous. Atwood, Sanford S.; American Meat Institute., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Morton Adams. Adams, Morton; Perkins, James A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Agricultural Research Advisory Committee. United States Agency for International Development; New York State College of Agriculture, Agricultural Research Advisory Committee., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Agency for International Development. Hearne, Cannon C.; United States, Agency for International Development; Bolivia; Ghana., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Agency for International Development, Committee for Rural Development and Agricultural Research. Parker, Frank W.; Turk, Kenneth L.; United States, Agency for International Development., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Agency for International Development, Advisory Committee., 1963 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science. Sprague, Howard B., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - American Breeders Service. Milliman, Thomas E., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - B Miscellaneous. Beneway, Frank W.; Professional Studies Institute., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Bennett, Charles Dana. Foundation for American Agriculture., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - C Miscellaneous. Park, Roy H.; Carmichael, Oliver C.; Central Soya Company., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Cauliflower. Residues., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Cauliflower Issue. Semel, Maurice; Insecticides; Endrin; Pesticide residues., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Climatologists and Meteorologists. Pack, A. Boyd; Dethier, Bernard E.; National Academy of Sciences, Committee on Atmospheric Sciences., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Comprehensive Dairy Program for New York. Dairy industry., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Christmas Tree Growers. Serra, William W.; National Christmas Tree Growers Association; Christmas tree industry., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Crop Quality Control., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - D Miscellaneous. Darsie, Richard F.; Doxiadis Associates; Greece., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - E Miscellaneous. Evans, H.J.; Eastman, Edward R., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Eastern Milk Producers Cooperative Association., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Educational TV. Phillips, Elmer S., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Egg Clearing House. Miller, Hermon I.; Egg industry., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Empire Livestock Marketing Cooperative., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Empire State Soil Fertility Association. Hoekstra, John K., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Entomological Society of America. Hannah, H.W., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - F Miscellaneous. Franclemont, John G., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Farm Bureau Annual Meeting, 12 NOV 1963. Meade, Fay J.; New York Farm Bureau., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Farm-City Week., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Farm Credit Banks of Springfield. Cameron, Gordon., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Feed Grain Program., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Food and Drug Administration. Larrick, George P.; United States Food and Drug Administration; National Congress on Medical Quackery., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Food Power USA, Central Soya. Central Soya Company., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Food Systems of the Future. Buck, Paul A., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Ford Foundation. Hill, F.F., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Ford Foundation. Gamboa, Maria T.; Gamble, William K., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Forest Land Use Conference. Carlaw, James B., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Secretary Freeman's Speech at Syracuse 1 OCT 1963. Freeman, Orville L., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - G Miscellaneous. Plant Products Corporation., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Genesee Valley Regional Market Authority. King, Joseph P., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Georgia Outdoor Recreation Experiment Station., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Grange League Federation. Milliman, Thomas E.; Fallon, Edmund H.; Prosser, Arthur E.; Ranney, Warren A.; Egg industry; Poultry industry., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Grange League Federation Eastern States Merger. Ranney, Warren A.; Park, Roy H.; Grange League Federation; Eastern States Farmers' Exchange; Agway, Inc., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Grange League Federation Centennial Gift. Ranney, Warren A.; Cornell University Centennial Fund Campaign., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Grange League Federation Salmonella Derby Problem on Eggs., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Governor's Office. Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Aldrich, Alexander., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Study of the Grange Service Contest Reports in New York State., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - H Miscellaneous. Hamilton, Thomas H., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Holstein-Friesian Association of America. Rumler, Robert H., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Hudson Valley Fruit Investigation. Barton, Donald W.; Fraleigh, Elmore; Fruit industry., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Intercounty Fanners Cooperative Association. Johndrew, O.F., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Insecticide and Fungicide Conference. Hazen, Myron S.; Tobacco By-products and Chemical Corporation., 1939-64 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - National Science Foundation, International Biological Program., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Israel Project. National and University Institute of Agriculture., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - J Miscellaneous. James, H. Brooks., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Jaycees. Madgett, Robb., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - K Miscellaneous. Knapp, Halsey B.; Kwok, Jean., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - L Miscellaneous. Lerch, Donald; Logothetis, Clerhos; Lovely, Alice E., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Agricultural Enrollment in Land-grant Colleges and Universities., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Livestock Production in New York., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - McDonald Farm. J.M. McDonald Foundation., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Metropolitan Dairy Institute., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Milk Legislation. Kennedy, W. Keith; Fox, J. Russell; New York State Milk Distributors, Inc.; Dairy industry., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Monroe County Extension. Van Voorhis, Norman., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - N Miscellaneous. Grossman, Lawrence K.; National Broadcasting Company., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Naegele, John A. Pimentel, David., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Agricultural Board. Sharp, Paul F., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - National Agricultural Chemicals Association. Brinkley, Parke C., 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - National Canners Association., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - National Grange. Larson, Olaf F.; Newsom, Herschel D., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - National Potato Council. Mercker, A.E.; Potato Association of America; Potato industry., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - National Sanitation Foundation. Vaughan, Henry F., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation, Educational Policy in Agriculture. Kellogg, Charles E., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation Support. Morse, Roger A., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Navy Reserve Officers Training Course. Zalewski, C.V., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - New York Artificial Breeders' Cooperative. Earl, J. Stanley., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - New York Farmer Award. Wendell, Francis A.; Reid, J. Thomas; Merrill, Leland G., 1963-63 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - New York State Agricultural Businessmen's Council. Adams, Morton; Fox, J. Russell., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - New York State Canners and Freezers Association. Tyler, W.D., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations. Foster, Edward S., 1964-65 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New York State Exposition. Creal, Harold L., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - New York Farm Bureau. Foster, Edward S., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - New York State Nurserymen's Association. Stengler, Bernard B., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - New York State Flower Growers. Wilton, Charles., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - New York State Pesticide Control Board. Pomeroy, R. Watson; Pesticides., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - New York State Pesticide Control Board. Swanson, Gustav A.; Insecticides., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - New York State Dept, of Agriculture and Markets. Wickham, Donald J.; Stone, John H.; Driggs, Leslie W., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - New York State Bills. Corbin, Sol Neil., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - New York State Conservation Dept. Wilm, Harold G.; Heacox, Cecil E.; Wood industry., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - New York State Forest Practice Board. Hamilton, Lawrence S., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Northeast Agriculture Farm Credit. United States, Farm Credit Administration., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - New York State Executive Department, Policies and Procedures for Use of State-owned Cars., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - P Miscellaneous. Prosser, Arthur E.; Perkins, Frances., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - People to People Tour to Russia. Beals, Harlo P., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Pepsi-Cola Company. Sugar beet industry., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Potato Disagreement. Kearl, Delmar; Potato industry., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - R Miscellaneous. Smith, Vernon A.; Ritcher, Paul 0.; C.W. Robinson and Company., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Robison, Congressman Howard. Metz, Joseph F.; Robison, Howard W.; Milk marketing., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Rockefeller Foundation. Grant, U.J.; Osier, Robert., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - S Miscellaneous. Smith, Rebe Biggs., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Soil Conservation Society of America. Stark, Frank B., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - STAMINA, State Municipal and Industrial Action. Keating, Kenneth B.; Sugar beet industry; Air pollution., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Sugar Beet Feasibility Study. Sugar beet industry; Mechanical harvesting., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - SUNY. Murray, J. Lawrence., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - SUNY, Miscellaneous. Race relations., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - SUNY, Board of Trustees., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 39-40)
  - SUNY, Unit Heads Meeting. Murray, Lawrence., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - T Miscellaneous. Todd, Walter L.; Tennessee Valley Authority., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - "The Role of the United States Dept, of Agriculture in Research and Education." Brady, Nyle C., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - United States House of Representatives, House Select Committee on Government Research., 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 44)